eagleget.com 2019-08-26

# Privacy Policy - EagleGet

**The following privacy policy applies to both EagleGet and iTab.**

When do we collect information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

– To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

How do we protect visitor information?

– We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like names, email addresses or credit card numbers.  
– We use regular Malware Scanning.

Do we use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won’t affect the user’s experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still place orders .

Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

TOS  
1  
In return for some of the premium features of Eagleget, you may choose to be a peer on the Luminati network. By doing so you agree to have read and accepted the terms of service of the [Luminati SDK SLA](http://luminati.io/legal/sdk-sla). You may opt out of the network from settings

2  
‘Your use of Eagleget is free of charge in exchange for safely using some of your device’s resources, and only when you are not using your device. You may turn this off from the settings menu. Please see our TOS for further information. [Luminati SDK SLA](http://luminati.io/legal/sdk-sla)

Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.

How does our site handle do not track signals?  
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?  
It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via email  
– Within 7 business days  
We will notify the users via in-site notification  
– Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

For user privacy statement of EagleGet software, please refer to [EagleGet User Experience Program](http://www.eagleget.com/eagleget-user-experience-program-euep/)
